RG 161:001, Connecticut State Police
Connecticut State Library
- Series 7. Connecticut State Police Troop E, 1924-2000; 63 cubic feet
  - 1989-030, 58 cubic feet
    - Call log books
      - 1946 May 9-July 12 (Volume Volume 17)
      - 1946 July 12-September 14 (Volume Volume 18)
      - 1946 September 14-November 18 (Volume Volume 19)
      - 1946 November 18-1947 March 8 (Volume Volume 20)
      - 1947 March 8-June 12 (Volume Volume 21)
      - 1947 June 13-August 9 (Volume Volume 22)
      - 1947 August 9-October 6 (Volume Volume 23)
      - 1947 October 6-December 2 (Volume Volume 24)
      - 1947 December 2-1948 January 27 (Volume Volume 25)
      - 1948 January 27-March 26 (Volume Volume 26)
      - 1948 March 26-May 28 (Volume Volume 27)
      - 1948 May 28-July 24 (Volume Volume 28)
      - 1948 July 24-September 13 (Volume Volume 29)
      - 1948 September 13-November 12 (Volume Volume 30)
      - 1948 November 12-1949 February 24 (Volume Volume 31)
      - 1949 February 24-May 25 (Volume Volume 32)
      - 1949 May 25-August 12 (Volume Volume 33)
      - 1949 August 12-October 29 (Volume Volume 34)
      - 1949 October 29-1950 January 25 (Volume Volume 35)
      - 1950 January 25-April 19 (Volume Volume 36)
      - 1950 April 19-July 3 (Volume Volume 37)
      - 1950 July 3-September 8 (Volume Volume 38)
      - 1950 September 8-November 21 (Volume Volume 39)
      - 1950 November 21-1951 February 10 (Volume Volume 40)
      - 1951 February 10-April 18 (Volume Volume 41)
      - 1951 April 18-June 17 (Volume Volume 42)
      - 1951 June 17-August 19 (Volume Volume 43)
      - 1951 August 19-October 25 (Volume Volume 44)
      - 1951 October 25-December 20 (Volume Volume 45)
      - 1951 December 20-1952 February 19 (Volume Volume 46)
      - 1952 February 19-May 5 (Volume Volume 47)
      - 1952 May 6-July 10 (Volume Volume 48)
      - 1952 July 10-September 11 (Volume Volume 49)
      - 1952 September 12-November 24 (Volume Volume 50)
      - 1952 November 24-1953 February 2 (Volume Volume 51)
      - 1953 February 2-April 13 (Volume Volume 52)
      - 1953 April 14-June 20 (Volume Volume 53)
      - 1953 June 21-August 24 (Volume Volume 54)
      - 1953 August 24-October 22 (Volume Volume 55)
      - 1953 October 22-December 24 (Volume Volume 56)
      - 1953 December 24-1954 March 1 (Volume Volume 57)
      - 1954 March 1-May 7 (Volume Volume 58)
      - 1954 May 8-July 13 (Volume Volume 59)
      - 1954 July 13-September 15 (Volume Volume 60)
      - 1954 September 16-October 23 (Volume Volume 61)
      - 1954 October 23-December 27 (Volume Volume 62)
      - 1954 December 27-1955 March 8 (Volume Volume 63)
      - 1955 March 8-May 16 (Volume Volume 64)
      - 1955 May 16-July 20 (Volume Volume 65)
      - 1955 July 20-September 28 (Volume Volume 66)
      - 1955 September 28-December 8 (Volume Volume 67)
      - 1955 December 8-1956 March 6 (Volume Volume 68)
      - 1956 March 6-June 7 (Volume Volume 69)
      - 1956 June 8-August 21 (Volume Volume 70)
      - 1956 August 22-October 24 (Volume Volume 71)
      - 1956 October 24-1957 January 4 (Volume Volume 72)
      - 1957 January 5-March 26 (Volume Volume 73)
      - 1957 March 26-June 4 (Volume Volume 74)
      - 1957 June 4-August 8 (Volume Volume 75)
      - 1957 August 8-October 12 (Volume Volume 76)
      - 1957 October 12-December 18 (Volume Volume 77)
      - 1957 December 18-1958 February 22 (Volume Volume 78)
      - 1958 February 22-April 25 (Volume Volume 79)
      - 1958 April 25-June 22 (Volume Volume 80)
      - 1958 June 23-August 18 (Volume Volume 81)
      - 1958 August 18-October 14 (Volume Volume 82)
      - 1958 October 14-December 8 (Volume Volume 83)
      - 1958 December 8-1959 February 6 (Volume Volume 84)
      - 1959 February 6-1959 April 7 (Volume Volume 85)
      - 1959 April 7-June 3 (Volume Volume 86)
      - 1959 June 3-July 22 (Volume Volume 87)
      - 1959 July 22-September 8 (Volume Volume 88)
      - 1959 September 9-November 2 (Volume Volume 89)
      - 1959 November 2-December 23 (Volume Volume 90)
      - 1959 December 23-1960 February 25 (Volume Volume 91)
      - 1960 February 25-April 23 (Volume Volume 92)
      - 1960 April 23-June 15 (Volume Volume 93)
      - 1960 June 16-August 4 (Volume Volume 94)
      - 1960 August 4-October 2 (Volume Volume 95)
      - 1960 October 2-December 5 (Volume Volume 96)
      - 1960 December 5-1961 February 16 (Volume Volume 97)
      - 1961 February 16-May 5 (Volume Volume 98)
      - 1961 May 5-1961 July 9 (Volume Volume 99)
      - 1961 July 9-September 7 (Volume Volume 100)
      - 1961 September 7-December 1 (Volume Volume 101)
      - 1961 December 1-1962 March 13 (Volume Volume 102)
      - 1962 March 3-June 16 (Volume Volume 103)
      - 1962 June 16-September 8 (Volume Volume 104)
      - 1962 September 9-December 8 (Volume Volume 105)
      - 1962 December 8-1963 March 16 (Volume Volume 106)
      - 1963 March 16-June 9 (Volume Volume 107)
      - 1963 June 9-August 9 (Volume Volume 108)
      - 1963 August 9-October 15 (Volume Volume 109)
      - 1963 October 16-December 27 (Volume Volume 110)
      - 1963 December 27-1964 March 14 (Volume Volume 111)
      - 1964 March 14-May 27 (Volume Volume 112)
      - 1964 May 27-July 30 (Volume Volume 113)
      - 1964 July 30-October 6 (Volume Volume 114)
      - 1964 October 6-December 16 (Volume Volume 115)
      - 1964 December 16-1965 March 3 (Volume Volume 116)
      - 1965 March 3-May 11 (Volume Volume 117)
      - 1965 May 11-July 17 (Volume Volume 118)
      - 1965 July 17-September 24 (Volume Volume 119)
      - 1965 September 24-December 23 (Volume Volume 120)
      - 1965 December 23-1966 March 24 (Volume Volume 121)
      - 1966 March 25-June 26 (Volume Volume 122)
      - 1966 June 26-September 6 (Volume Volume 123)
      - 1966 September 6-December 2 (Volume Volume 124)
      - 1966 December 2-1967 March 6 (Volume Volume 125)
      - 1967 March 6-May 31 (Volume Volume 126)
      - 1967 May 31-August 12 (Volume Volume 127)
      - 1967 August 13-November 1 (Volume Volume 128)
      - 1967 November 1-1968 February 4 (Volume Volume 129)
      - 1968 February 4-April 28 (Volume Volume 130)
      - 1968 April 28-July 21 (Volume Volume 131)
      - 1968 July 21-October 12 (Volume Volume 132)
      - 1968 October 12-1969 January 21 (Volume Volume 133)
      - 1969 January 21-May 3 (Volume Volume 134)
        No volume for 1969 May 4-August 1.
      - 1969 August 2-November 2 (Volume Volume 135)
      - 1969 November 2-December 31 (Volume Volume 136)
      - 1970 January-April 14 (Volume Volume 137)
      - 1970 April 14-July 18 (Volume Volume 138)
      - 1970 July 19-October 17 (Volume Volume 139)
      - 1970 October 17-1971 January 22 (Volume Volume 140)
      - 1971 January 22-April 28 (Volume Volume 141)
      - 1971 April 28-August 6 (Volume Volume 142)
      - 1971 August 6-1971 November 19 (Volume Volume 143)
      - 1971 November 20-February 22 (Volume Volume 144)
      - 1972 February 23-May 17 (Volume Volume 145)
      - 1972 May 18-July 13 (Volume Volume 146)
      - 1972 July 13-September 9 (Volume Volume 147)
      - 1972 September 9-November 18 (Volume Volume 148)
      - 1972 November 18-1973 January 22 (Volume Volume 149)
      - 1973 January 22-March 26 (Volume Volume 150)
      - 1973 March 26-May 18 (Volume Volume 151)
      - 1973 May 19-July 10 (Volume Volume 152)
      - 1973 July 10-September 1 (Volume Volume 153)
      - 1973 September 1-October 22 (Volume Volume 154)
      - 1973 October 23-December 20 (Volume Volume 155)
      - 1973 December 20-1974 February 21 (Volume Volume 156)
      - 1974 February 21-April 23 (Volume Volume 157)
      - 1974 April 23-June 16 (Volume Volume 158)
      - 1974 June 17-August 4 (Volume Volume 159)
      - 1974 August 4-September 19 (Volume Volume 160)
      - 1974 September 19-November 10 (Volume Volume 161)
      - 1974 November 10-December 31 (Volume Volume 162)
      - 1974 December 31-1975 February 20 (Volume Volume 163)
      - 1975 February 20-April 10 (Volume Volume 164)
      - 1975 April 10-May 26 (Volume Volume 165)
      - 1975 May 26-July 5 (Volume Volume 166)
      - 1975 July 6-August 15 (Volume Volume 167)
      - 1975 August 15-October 4 (Volume Volume 168)
      - 1975 October 4-November 22 (Volume Volume 169)
      - 1975 November 22-1976 January 17 (Volume Volume 170)
      - 1976 January 17-March 10 (Volume Volume 171)
      - 1976 March 10-May 3 (Volume Volume 172)
      - 1976 May 4-June 19 (Volume Volume 173)
      - 1976 June 19-August 11 (Volume Volume 174)
      - 1976 August 11-October 11 (Volume Volume 175)
      - 1976 October 12-December 22 (Volume Volume 176)
      - 1976 December 22-1977 February 25 (Volume Volume 177)
      - 1977 February 25-April 29 (Volume Volume 178)
      - 1977 April 29-June 29 (Volume Volume 179)
      - 1977 June 29-August 23 (Volume Volume 180)
      - 1977 August 23-October 24 (Volume Volume 181)
      - 1977 October 25-December 21 (Volume Volume 182)
      - 1977 December 22-1978 February 19 (Volume Volume 183)
      - 1978 February 19-April 23 (Volume Volume 184)
      - 1978 April 23-June 21 (Volume Volume 185)
      - 1978 June 21-August 12 (Volume Volume 186)
      - 1978 August 12-October 8 (Volume Volume 187)
      - 1978 October 8-November 15 (Volume Volume 188)
  - 2013-039, 5 cubic feet
    - Case books
      - 1985 January 26-1988 October 25, 6 volumes (Box 1)
      - 1988 October 25-1991 August 20, 6 volumes (Box 2)
      - 1991 August 20-1994 October 22, 6 volumes (Box 3)
      - 1994 October 22-1997 September 1, 6 volumes (Box 4)
      - 1997 September 1-2000 June 27, 6 volumes (Box 5)
- Series 8. Connecticut State Police Troop F, 1954-1999; 2013-029; 24 cubic feet
  - Call log books
    - 1954 December 10-1955 December 25, 8 volumes (Box 1)
    - 1955 December 25-1957 February 27, 7 volumes (Box 2)
    - 1957 February 27-1958 June 15, 6 volumes (Box 3)
    - 1958 June 16-1959 November 26, 6 volumes (Box 4)
    - 1959 November 27-1961 July 13, 6 volumes (Box 5)
    - 1961 July 13-1962 November 24, 6 volumes (Box 6)
    - 1962 November 24-1964 March 24, 6 volumes (Box 7)
    - 1964 March 23-1965 June 26, 6 volumes (Box 8)
    - 1965 June 26-1966 September 30, 6 volumes (Box 9)
    - 1966 September 30-1968 February 10, 6 volumes (Box 10)
    - 1968 February 10-1969 June 21, 6 volumes (Box 11)
    - 1969 June 21-1970 December 7, 6 volumes (Box 12)
    - 1970 December 7-1972 February 28, 5 volumes (Box 13)
    - 1972 February 29-1973 June 12, 6 volumes (Box 14)
    - 1973 June 12-1974 August 12, 6 volumes (Box 15)
    - 1974 August 12-1975 July 3, 5 volumes (Box 16)
    - 1975 July 3-1976 July 15, 5 volumes (Box 17)
    - 1976 July 16-1977 September 19, 5 volumes (Box 18)
    - 1977 September 19-November 13, 1 volume (Box 19)
  - Arrest log books
    - 1977 November 14-1986 April 25, 5 volumes (Box 19)
    - 1986 April 26-1990 June 29, 5 volumes (Box 20)
    - 1990 June 30-1995 March 12, 6 volumes (Box 21)
    - 1995 March 12-1999 December 31, 6 volumes (Box 22)
  - Case books
    - 1946-1978, 7 volumes (Box 23)
    - 1972-1994, 12 volumes (Box 24)
- Series 9. Connecticut State Police Troop G, 1939-1999; 2013-038; 35 cubic feet
  - Call log books
    - 1939 April 3-1941 October 31, 5 volumes (Box 1)
    - 1941 November 1-1943 September 4, 4 volumes (Box 2)
    - 1943 September 4-1945 July 29, 6 volumes (Box 3)
    - 1945 July 29-1948 February 27, 7 volumes (Box 4)
    - 1948 February 28-1950 January 23, 8 volumes (Box 5)
    - 1950 January 23-1951 April 7, 6 volumes (Box 6)
    - 1951 April 7-1952 July 1, 5 volumes (Box 7)
    - 1952 July 1-1953 September 9, 5 volumes (Box 8)
    - 1953 September 9-1955 February 1, 5 volumes (Box 9)
    - 1955 February 1-1956 October 3, 6 volumes (Box 10)
    - 1956 February 6-1959 June 30, 1 volume (Box 35)
    - 1956 October 3-1957 October 20, 5 volumes (Box 11)
    - 1957 October 20-1958 June 26, 5 volumes (Box 12)
    - 1958 June 26-1959 March 18, 5 volumes (Box 13)
    - 1959 March 18-1960 September 30, 7 volumes (Box 14)
    - 1960 September 30-1961 October 16, 5 volumes (Box 15)
    - 1961 October 16-1962 December 2, 6 volumes (Box 16)
    - 1962 December 2-1963 November 29, 5 volumes (Box 17)
    - 1963 November 29-1964 November 5, 5 volumes (Box 18)
    - 1964 November 5-1965 September 12, 5 volumes (Box 19)
    - 1965 September 12-1966 October 28, 6 volumes (Box 20)
    - 1966 October 28-1968 January 24, 6 volumes (Box 21)
    - 1968 January 24-1969 May 9, 6 volumes (Box 22)
    - 1969 May 9-1970 June 19, 6 volumes (Box 23)
    - 1970 June 19-1971 August 28, 6 volumes (Box 24)
    - 1971 August 28-1972 October 18, 6 volumes (Box 25)
    - 1972 October 18-1973 October 4, 6 volumes (Box 26)
    - 1973 October 4-1974 October 30, 5 volumes (Box 27)
    - 1974 October 30-1975 October 5, 6 volumes (Box 28)
    - 1975 October 5-1976 December 18, 6 volumes (Box 29)
    - 1976 December 18-1978 April 24, 6 volumes (Box 30)
    - 1978 April 25-December 18, 3 volumes + 1 partial (Box 31)
      The volume for 11/30/1978-4/16/1981 begins with call logs and ends with arrest logs.
  - Arrest log books
    - 1978 December 19-1984 August 30, 2 volumes + 1 partial (Box 31)
    - 1984 August 31-1989 March 20, 6 volumes (Box 32)
    - 1989 March 20-1993 May 29, 6 volumes (Box 33)
    - 1993 May 30-1999 April 7, 7 volumes (Box 34)
  - Case books, 1959-1978; 14 volumes (Box 35)
- Series 10. Connecticut State Police Troop H, 1938-2000; 2013-035; 38 cubic feet
  - Call log books
    - 1938 July 15-1940 November 4, 4 volumes (Box 1)
    - 1941 April 15-1943 October 5, 5 volumes (Box 2)
    - 1943 October 5-1946 May 30, 5 volumes (Box 3)
    - 1946 June 1-1947 December 19, 7 volumes (Box 4)
    - 1947 December 20-1949 June 22, 6 volumes (Box 5)
    - 1949 September 26-1950 October 11, 4 volumes (Box 6)
    - 1951 January 24-1952 April 8, 6 volumes (Box 7)
    - 1952 April 9-1953 April 16, 5 volumes (Box 8)
    - 1953 June 9-1954 July 18, 7 volumes (Box 9)
    - 1954 July 18-1955 September 10, 5 volumes (Box 10)
    - 1955 September 10-1957 February 6, 5 volumes (Box 11)
    - 1957 February 7-1958 July 22, 5 volumes (Box 12)
    - 1958 July 23-1959 October 30, 5 volumes (Box 13)
    - 1959 October 30-1960 July 8, 3 volumes (Box 14)
    - 1960 October 9-1962 February 11, 5 volumes (Box 15)
    - 1962 February 12-1963 January 19, 4 volumes (Box 16)
    - 1963 January 19-September 12, 2 volumes (Box 17)
    - 1965 December 19-1966 May 8, 2 volumes (Box 18)
    - 1966 May 8-1967 February 6, 4 volumes (Box 19)
    - 1967 February 7-1968 March 13, 4 volumes (Box 20)
    - 1968 March 13-1969 May 27, 6 volumes (Box 21)
    - 1969 May 28-1970 June 13, 5 volumes (Box 22)
    - 1970 June 13-1971 September 12, 5 volumes (Box 23)
    - 1971 September 13-1972 June 23, 5 volumes (Box 24)
    - 1972 June 23-1973 May 17, 6 volumes (Box 25)
    - 1973 May 17-1974 March 8, 5 volumes (Box 26)
    - 1974 May 7-1975 March 10, 5 volumes (Box 27)
    - 1975 February 19-November 30, 5 volumes (Box 28)
    - 1975 November 30-1976 September 14, 5 volumes (Box 29)
    - 1976 September 13-1977 April 13, 4 volumes (Box 30)
  - Arrest log books
    - 1983-1985, 5 volumes (Box 31)
    - 1986-1988, 6 volumes (Box 32)
    - 1989-1991, 6 volumes (Box 33)
    - 1992-1994, 6 volumes (Box 34)
    - 1995-1997, 5 volumes (Box 35)
    - 1998-2000, 6 volumes (Box 36)
  - Case books
    - 1942-1957 June 30, 11 volumes (Box 37)
    - 1957 July 1-1969, 11 volumes (Box 38)
  - Emergency telephone log books
    - 1941 June 9-1945 March 25, 2 volumes (Box 2)
    - 1954 August 3-1960 April 4, 1 volume (Box 10)
- Series 11. Connecticut State Police Troop I, 1935-1997; 2013-034; 32 cubic feet
  - Call log books
    - 1935 April 16-1938 March 9, 5 volumes (Box 1)
    - 1941 January 1-1943 August 17, 4 volumes (Box 2)
    - 1943 August 18-1946 September 5, 7 volumes (Box 3)
    - 1946 September 5-1948 August 25, 8 volumes (Box 4)
    - 1948 August 25-1950 March 25, 9 volumes (Box 5)
    - 1950 March 26-1951 November 30, 9 volumes (Box 6)
    - 1951 December 1-1953 June 2, 6 volumes (Box 7)
    - 1953 June 2-1954 October 14, 6 volumes (Box 8)
    - 1954 October 15-1956 February 11, 6 volumes (Box 9)
    - 1956 February 11-1957 June 26, 6 volumes (Box 10)
    - 1957 June 26-1959 February 24, 6 volumes (Box 11)
    - 1959 February 24-1960 September 22, 6 volumes (Box 12)
    - 1960 September 23-1962 February 19, 6 volumes (Box 13)
    - 1962 February 19-1963 October 19, 6 volumes (Box 14)
    - 1963 October 19-1965 August 11, 6 volumes (Box 15)
    - 1965 August 11-1967 July 14, 6 volumes (Box 16)
    - 1967 July 14-1969 March 10, 6 volumes (Box 17)
    - 1969 March 10-1970 July 31, 6 volumes (Box 18)
    - 1970 July 31-1971 September 2, 5 volumes (Box 19)
    - 1971 September 3-1972 August 27, 6 volumes (Box 20)
    - 1972 August 27-1973 August 3, 6 volumes (Box 21)
    - 1973 August 4-1974 July 28, 6 volumes (Box 22)
    - 1974 July 29-1975 August 10, 6 volumes (Box 23)
    - 1975 August 10-1976 October 31, 6 volumes (Box 24)
    - 1976 November 1-1978 May 27, 5 volumes (Box 25)
    - 1978 May 27-December 5, 3 volumes (Box 26)
  - Arrest log books
    - 1978 December 6-1986 January 15, 3 volumes (Box 26)
    - 1986 January 16-1991 October 15, 6 volumes (Box 27)
    - 1991 October 19-1997 March 26, 6 volumes (Box 28)
  - Case books
    - 1945-1962 June 30, 10 volumes (Box 29)
    - 1962 July 1-1969, 9 volumes (Box 30)
    - 1970-1979, 13 volumes (Box 31)
  - Toll log books, 1946-1963; 6 volumes (Box 32)
- Series 12. Connecticut State Police Troop K, 1938-2002; 2013-025; 31 cubic feet
  This entire series except for the Air Defense warning test log book, missing persons log book, and Emergency Service Unit (ESU) log book is RESTRICTED per Connecticut General Statutes §54-142a.
  - Case books
    - 1938 December 18-1964 July 20, 13 volumes (Box 1)
    - 1964 July 1-1971 December 15, 14 volumes (Box 2)
    - 1972 January 1-1977 September 15, 13 volumes (Box 3)
  - Dispatch log books
    - 1938 December 7-1943 July 31, 9 volumes (Box 4)
    - 1943 August 1-1946 March 19, 7 volumes (Box 5)
    - 1946 March 19-1947 December 19, 9 volumes (Box 6)
    - 1947 December 20-1949 January 26, 7 volumes (Box 7)
    - 1949 January 26-1950 December 22, 6 volumes (Box 8)
    - 1950 December 22-1952 October 4, 6 volumes (Box 9)
    - 1952 November 17-1953 December 15, 8 volumes (Box 10)
    - 1953 December 15-1955 April 29, 8 volumes (Box 11)
    - 1955 April 30-1956 June 15, 7 volumes (Box 12)
    - 1956 June 15-1957 October 2, 5 volumes (Box 13)
    - 1957 October 3-1959 July 24, 6 volumes (Box 14)
    - 1959 July 24-1961 March 20, 6 volumes (Box 15)
    - 1961 March 21-1962 November 30, 6 volumes (Box 16)
    - 1962 November 30-1964 July 3, 6 volumes (Box 17)
    - 1964 July 3-1966 May 6, 6 volumes (Box 18)
    - 1966 May 6-1967 September 30, 6 volumes (Box 19)
    - 1967 September 30-1968 December 16, 6 volumes (Box 20)
    - 1968 December 16-1970 January 17, 6 volumes (Box 21)
    - 1970 January 17-1971 August 30, 6 volumes (Box 22)
    - 1971 August 30-1972 June 16, 6 volumes (Box 23)
    - 1972 June 16-1973 July 10, 6 volumes (Box 24)
    - 1973 July 11-1974 June 30, 6 volumes (Box 25)
    - 1974 June 30-1975 April 18, 6 volumes (Box 26)
    - 1975 April 18-1976 March 5, 6 volumes (Box 27)
    - 1976 March 5-1976 February 22, 5 volumes (Box 28)
    - 1977 February 22-1978 October 31, 4 volumes (Box 29)
  - Incident log books
    - 1978-1981, 10 volumes (Box 30)
    - 1982, 5 volumes (Box 31)
  - Air Defense warning test log book, 1956-1964; 1 volume (Box 31)
  - Arrest log book, 2001 July 16-2002 May 7; 1 volume (Box 31)
  - Missing persons log book, before 1970; 1 volume (Box 31)
  - Emergency Service Unit (ESU) log book, 1970 November-1975 June; 1 volume (Box 28)
- Series 13. Connecticut State Police Troop L, 1942-1999; 32 cubic feet
  - 2012-001, 30 cubic feet
    - Call log books
      Volume 1 was not transferred to the Connecticut State Library.
      - Volumes 2-15, 1942 June 20-1945 December 31 (Box 1)
      - Volumes 16-24, 1946 January 1-1948 November 13 (Box 2)
      - Volumes 25-31, 1948 November 13-1951 July 24 (Box 3)
      - Volumes 32-37, 1951 July 24-1953 October 21 (Box 4)
      - Volumes 38-43, 1953 October 22-1956 February 2 (Box 5)
      - Volumes 44-49, 1956 February 3-1958 March 20 (Box 6)
      - Volumes 50-55, 1958 March 20-1960 February 6 (Box 7)
      - Volumes 56-61, 1960 February 6-1962 April 5 (Box 8)
      - Volumes 62-67, 1962 April 6-1964 June 9 (Box 9)
      - Volumes 68-73, 1964 June 9-1966 March 14 (Box 10)
      - Volumes 74-79, 1966 March 14-1967 August 26 (Box 11)
      - Volumes 80-85, 1967 August 26-1968 October 2 (Box 12)
      - Volumes 86-91, 1968 October 2-1969 July 26 (Box 13)
      - Volumes 92-97, 1969 July 27-1970 August 5 (Box 14)
      - Volumes 98-103, 1970 August 5-1971 October 21 (Box 15)
      - Volumes 104-109, 1971 October 22-1973 February 8 (Box 16)
      - Volumes 110-115, 1973 February 8-December 31 (Box 17)
      - Volumes 116-119, 1973 December 31-1974 June 30 (Box 18)
      - Volumes 123-125, 1974 October 1-1974 November 12 (Box 19A)
        Includes information from Troops A and B.
      - Volumes 164-167, 1975 July 23-1976 January 30 (Box 20)
      - Volumes 168-173, 1976 January 30-December 15 (Box 21)
      - Volumes 174-179, 1976 December 15-1977 December 6 (Box 22)
      - Volumes 180-185, 1977 December 6-1979 April 30 (Box 23)
    - Incident log sheets
      Arranged by incident number.
      Includes incidents from Troops A and B.
      - Items 133-142, incidents 016218-021539, 1974 December 30-1975 March 9 (Box 19B)
      - Items 143-151, incidents 021540-026377, 1975 March 10-May 11 (Box 19C)
      - Items 152-159, incidents 026378-031693, 1975 May 12-July 6 (Box 19D)
      - Items 160-163, incidents 031694-033539, 1975 July 7-August 4 (Box 19E)
    - Arrest log books
      - 1974 July 2-1975 August 5, 1 volume (Box 18)
        Includes arrests from Troops A and B.
        No volume number.
      - Volumes A1-A6, 1979 May 2-1989 March 19 (Box 24)
      - Volumes A7-A11, 1989 March 19-1993 August 6 (Box 25)
      - Volumes A12-A17, 1993 August 6-1999 December 9 (Box 26)
  - 2013-037, 2 cubic feet
    - Case books
      - 1945-1972, 13 volumes (Box 1)
      - 1973-1984, 12 volumes (Box 2)
- Series 14. Training Material, 1950-1951; 2008-013
  - Connecticut State Police Auxiliary Training Course handout, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Box Shared box)